Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - E Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    Eisenhower, Milton S.; Office of War Information.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    Cutler, Robert; United States Dept. of War; Farm labor.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    O'Neal, Edward A.; Farm Security Administration.
  - Farm Foundation., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    Lowden, Frank O.; Taylor, Henry C.
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    Hunger, Henry H.; Gillett, Alien L.; Thomson, Edward H.; Milk prices.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Grange League Federation., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    McConnell, James A.; Milliman, Thomas E.
  - New York State Grange., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    Rich, W.J.
  - National Grange., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    Gardner, Charles M.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - New York State Horticultural Society., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - I Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    Selective Service.
  - Ithaca Savings Bank., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    Gredel, Henry W.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    Wilson, M.L.; Lloyd, W.A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service.
  - Executive Committee., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    Cooper, Thomas P.; Walton, T.O.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Farm labor.
  - Committee on Relationships., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    Davis, Chester C.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; War Food Administration.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    Moffat, Abbot Low.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    New York State War Fund.
  - Near East Foundation., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Archer, Laird.
  - O Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    Schoellkopf, Paul A.; Subasic, Ivan; Lehman, Herbert H.; Conscientious objectors.
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association, Inc., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    Truman, Harry S.; Treman, Robert E.; Thayer, Frank E.; World War II.
  - V Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - WGY., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1942-43 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Laws of New York and United States [pamphlets], 1904-1945 (Box 25)